

# YEHOR KHOLODIUK

### CONTACT

Limassol, 3105 Cyprus **Mobile:** +35799077536

egor.kholodiuk@gmail.com

#### LINKS

- https://www.linkedin.com /in/yehor-kholodiuk-9bbb6238/
- https://github.com /YehorKholodiuk

## **EDUCATION**

June 2021
Front End Development
Programming Academy in Silicon
Valley (PASV), Sunnyvale,
California, USA.

- Certificate for the successful completion of the JavaScript Syntax course. (Completion date -July, 20, 2020) – proficient knowledge.
- Certificate for the successful completion of the JavaScript Practice course.(Completion date – December 1, 2020) – proficient knowledge.
- Certificate for the successful completion of the Front-End React course. (Completion date – June, 2021) – proficient knowledge.

Other courses that have been undertaken and successfully completed:

- HTML, CSS Syntax proficient knowledge.
- Express JS proficient

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Hi, my name is Yehor Kholodiuk.

I am Front-End Developer.

My technologies are ReactJs, JavaScript, TypeScript.

After years of unemployment I found myself in coding.

I have strong will to learn new technologies and achieve new goals and create new things, so this was the reason for me to study Front End development.

I developed reusable components and participated in creation of CRM, SPA and different applications.

After completion of my previous project I worked as a freelancer. Besides being Front End Developer, I have knowledge and experience in the following Back-End technologies: Databases (Mongo DB, MySQL), REST API, server-side rendering (Express JS).

I have skills to quickly fix usability problems.

I have an experience with some testing tools, like Mocha, Chai and JEST. I am a qualified professional, who is success oriented and motivated. I live in Limassol, Cyprus. I have Cyprus citizenship and I don't need Cyprus work permit.

I am always ready to answer all your questions.

Best regards,

Yehor Kholodiuk.

#### **SKILLS**

- Redux
- React
- Bug Fixes
- JavaScript
- TypeScript

- HTML
- CSS
- BootStrap
- Git

# **WORK HISTORY**

June 2023 - Current **Front-End Developer**, *Freelancing*.

March 2022 - February 2023

# Front End Developer, PROTRADE CONSULTING GmbH (remote Position), Osnabruck, Germany

- Developed functional reusable React components for CRM System.
- Developed UI of online-store.
- Used Mocha and Chai for unit-testing.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to

knowledge.

- React Redux proficient knowledge.
- Mongo DB and Postman (experience with Restful API) – proficient knowledge.

June 2014 MBA: Business Administration CTL EUROCOLLEGE, Limassol. Cyprus.

June 2007
Bachelor of Science: Finance **Alfred Noble University**, Dnipro,
Ukraine.

2003

**Petro Mohyla Black Sea National University**, Ukraine, Mykolaiv.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Ukrainian, Russian: Native
language
English: C2
Proficient
Greek: A2
Elementary
German: B1
Intermediate

confirm creative proposals and design best practices.

- Teamed on user-centric design strategy in translation of UX and business requirements into coded solutions.
- Use regulatory and compliance standards for user interface designs.
- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.
- Promoted better component lifecycle practices.

August 2021 - January 2022

# Front-End Developer, LANARS (Custom Software Development Services) Remote Internship, Dnipro, Ukraine

- In order to improve performance of the application, I convinced team to implement different kind of state manager.
- Cooperated with 10+ senior developers in development and testing of the big scale application.
- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.
- Made recommendations for new technology integration based on suitability and alignment to business goals.
- Mastered practical use of Redux technology and optimized unit testing and development of functional components.

December 2010 - August 2014 **Back Office Specialist**, *PRIMECAP CYPRUS LIMITED*,
Limassol, Cyprus

#### **HOBBIES**

Coding, travelling, swimming, fitness.